{
    "id": "8ed47de35ed0440db10b48289f0e674e",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Run Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "e26dcc70302a4269977a45048b843d96",
            "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Run Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Can you get some sugar from the shop? We have run ………………",
                    "description": "To run out of something is to have none of it left.",
                    "answers": [
                        "off",
                        "out",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "This car runs ……………… petrol.",
                    "description": "When a car runs on petrol, it is powered by petrol.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "off",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The boy ran …………….. from home because he had no one to love him there.",
                    "description": "To run away is to escape or to run from somebody who is chasing you.",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "off",
                        "away"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Cancer runs ……………. his family. Both his parents died of it.",
                    "description": "If a disease runs in a family, it is kind of hereditary. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The police constable ran ………………. the thief but he could not catch him.",
                    "description": "To run after somebody is to chase them. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "out",
                        "after"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "When we were kids we would spend the entire afternoon running ……………. the neighborhood.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "around",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I want to run ……………… President.",
                    "description": "To run for President is to try to be elected President.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "for",
                        "after"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ran …………….. an old friend of mine yesterday.",
                    "description": "To run into somebody is to meet them unexpectedly.",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "into",
                        "over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Can you run ………………. hundred copies of this document?",
                    "description": "Run off can mean make photocopies.",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "off",
                        "about"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ran ………………. a dog while driving home from work.",
                    "description": "To run over a dog is to hit it with a vehicle.",
                    "answers": [
                        "after",
                        "over",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has run ……………… a huge debt on his credit cards.",
                    "description": "To run up debt is to spend a lot of money on credit.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "up",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ran ………………. the presentation one more time to ensure that everything is perfect.",
                    "description": "To run through a presentation is to practice it quickly.",
                    "answers": [
                        "through",
                        "over",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}